Sync by
지노
jin5a@naver.com
어바웃 타임
(About Time, 2013)
I always knew we
were a fairly odd family.
우리 가족은 꽤 별나다
First there was me.
일단 나부터
큰 키에 말랐고
머리는 오렌지색이다
Too tall. Too skinny.
Too orange.
엄만 사랑스럽지만
다른 엄마 같지 않다
My mum was lovely,
but not like other mums.
엄마에겐 뭔가
믿음직한 구석이 있다
There was
something solid about her.
독특하고 분주하며
냉담하다
Something rectangular,
busy and unsentimental.
엄마 패션 아이콘은
'영국 여왕'이다
Her fashion icon was the Queen.
아빠는 좀 더 평범하다
시간이 많이 남아돈다
Dad, well, he was more normal. He always
seemed to have time on his hands.
50살 생신 때
대학 강의를 접은 후로
After giving up teaching university
students on his 50th birthday,
한가로운 얘기나
탁구 게임에서
he was eternally available
for a leisurely chat or
늘 존재감을 발휘한다
to let me win at table tennis.
그렇지
Yes.